downloadoney.com 2014-09-18

# Privacy Policy | This site

_Privacy Policy_

1\. Processing of personal data provided via the Website 

EAD Consulting Ltd (“ **We** ” or the “ **Company** ” or “ **EADC** ”) informs users of its website [put website here] (the “ **Website** “), of its policy of protection of personal data regarding access and use by users of the Website that EADC places at the disposal of Internet users interested in its services and content, so that they can freely and voluntarily determine whether they wish to provide personal data to EADC which may be required or that may be obtained. 

We do not have access to any personal information except such such data that the user voluntarily sends to us when contacting EADC. We will never share your personal information and we only use it when responding to your specific inquiries. We will never send electronic communications for promotional purposes. 

2\. User Consent 

When filling out the form and clicking “send”, the user confirms to have read and expressly accepted the Website´s legal terms, and gives his or her unequivocal and explicit consent to the processing of personal data for the purposes set out here and the services provided by EADC. 

Also, the user expressly consents to the possibility that his or her opinions and content contributed to the Website will be treated by EADC for the purposes indicated herein. 

3\. Transfers 

We do not sell the personal information of our users to third parties for commercial purposes without the express consent of users. We might, however, disclose personal information to comply with legal requirements, enforce our policies, respond to legal claims relating to infringement by ads or other content of third party rights or to protect the rights of any person or their property or their safety. 

We can also share and disclose your personal information with members of the EADC group of companies, to provide content and services (like registration, transactions and customer support), to facilitate the prevention and detection of potentially illegal acts and violations of our policies, make decisions about their products, services and communications as well as in some cases, access to data by certain service providers who help with our business operations. In this sense, the user expressly consents the assignment of his or her personal data for the purposes specified in this Privacy Policy. 

4\. Data provided by minors 

For children 13 years years old and udner, the written consent from parents or guardians for the processing of your personal data is required, along with photocopy of their national ID card, which must be sent to the email address [privacidad@EADConsultine.es](mailto:privacidad@EADConsultine.es). In no case shall data with respect to the professional, economic or the privacy of other family members of a minor be collected, without their express consent. Only the data relating to the identity and address of parents or guardians of the user under fourteen years may be collected, with the sole purpose of obtaining the necessary authorisation. 

**If you are thirteen years old or under and you have accessed this Website without telling your parents or guardians, you must leave.**

5\. Security 

We inform users that we have adopted the necessary technical and organizational measures established by regulations to ensure the security of personal data and avoid its alteration, loss, or unauthorized access, given the state of technology, the nature of the data stored and the risks to which they are exposed, all in accordance with the provisions of the current applicable legislation and regulations. 

6\. Right of access, modification, opposition and cancellation of data 

You have the right to access your data held by us, modify it if the data is wrong, and to oppose certain treatments of data. 

These rights can be exercised via our email: [privacidad@EADConsulting.es](mailto:privacidad@EADConsulting.es), indicating the subject and request. 

The processing of personal data and the sending of commercial communications by electronic means are in compliance with current regulations. 

7\. Amendments to this Privacy Policy 

We reserve the right to amend this policy to adapt to future legislation or case law. 

8\. Governing Law 

Unless specific local law provides otherwise, this Privacy Policy and other terms and conditions relating to the Website are governed wholly by Spanish law. 

9\. Inquiries about this Policy 

Any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy can be sent by email to [privacidad@EADConsulting.es](mailto:privacidad@EADConsulting.es). 

10\. Inquiries about this Policy 

Cookies are text files of a small size, often encrypted, that a website stores on a computer or other device when accessing the website. Cookies may store the identification of the user that visited the site and the places that were navigated. 

When you revisit the site or website the cookies may be read in order to identify the user and to set the preferences and browser settings for that user. 

Failure to allow the use of cookies means that certain services or functionality of the website will not be available to the user. 

**This site uses the following cookies:**

· Session cookies to facilitate user navigation and remember where the user is when browsing a website. These cookies disappear once the navigation or session is concluded. 

· Cookies for authentication as a registered user to log on pages that require identification / authentication. These cookies are required to access restricted content services or users are identified and authenticated. 

· Analytics cookies (such as those of Google or Comscore). These cookies are used to analyse the visits made, places and times of website navigation. The cookie information is transmitted to and stored directly by the analytical providers on their servers. These cookies are used anonymously and to prepare website trend reports without identifying individual users. 

· Advertising Cookies. We use cookies to make advertising more attractive to users. Cookies are often used to select ads based on content that is relevant to a user, improve reporting of campaign performance and avoid showing ads that the user has already seen. Conversion cookies are also used so that advertisers may determine the number of times that people who click on the ads end up buying their products. These cookies allow EADC and the advertiser to know that you have clicked on the ad and that you have subsequently accessed the site of the advertiser. Some of our advertising products allow other companies send their own cookies to your browser. 

Any personal data that is collected through the use of cookies on this website will be processed by EAD Consulting, Ltd Spain, responsible to facilitate and improve browsing on the website, analyse visits and identify registered users. If you accept cookies you consent to the possible processing of personal data for all purposes indicated, international transfers and communications; but if you do not consent to such use then please do not accept the use of cookies. The user can exercise their rights of access, modification, cancellation and opposition to EADC at the above-mentioned address. 

You can set your browser to refuse or accept cookies, or set the browser so that cookies are automatically deleted once you close your browser, computer or device. You may change your cookies settings in browsers as follows: 

· Google Chrome Settings > Privacy > Content Settings > Cookies 

· Firefox Preferences > Privacy. 

· Internet Explorer under Tools > Internet Options > Privacy > Advanced. 

· Safari Preferences > Privacy. 

By accessing this website for the first time, without previously having cookies from this website, you will see a window informing you of the use of cookies and where you can view this “Cookies Policy”. If you close the window and continue browsing, you agree / consent to the use of cookies and these will be installed on your computer or device, otherwise cookies will not be installed and browsing and the service if this website will be limited. 

**For more information about the cookies used, contact the owner of this website at the address** [**contactos@EADConsulting.es**](mailto:contactos@EADConsulting.es)
